You'll make your own dinner,
because you don't have any friends.
- You were told, so make it.
- You make it. Yeah?
Just do what you're told.
Hey. Make your own dinner.
You make it.
- [Nagano] Here they go.
- [Ruru] Bo, that's dangerous.
[both grunting]
[Ma-kun] Wait. Wait, wait.
Wait. Wait.
Okay, fine. Wait a second.
[Bo] Sorry.
They sent me flying.
[Ruru] What the actual hell?
[Assun] You okay, Maririn? So ridiculous.
Should we go to the living room for now?
- Let's go.
- Yeah, let's go.
- What about our stuff?
- [Ruru] Ladies to the living room.
That was heated. Come with us.
[Ha-chan giggles]
Like I said…
BO (27)
COMMERCIAL PAINTER
…I'm not making his food.
He can do it.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Sorry, but I'm not going in there.
Right, Leo?
[Leo] There's no way.
I don't care what they tell us.
That's that then.
Let's go make our own food.
I'm not forgiving him, for real.
- Isn't it cute?
- Does everyone have their own seat?
- [Assun] It's not set in stone.
- [Ruru] Yeah, it's not decided.
- Are you okay?
- [Kazu-kun] Oh, I'm fine.
- Your chain…
- [Ruru] Did you fix it?
KAZU-KUN (29)
HOST CLUB OWNER
- No, it's fine. Just came off.
- [Hikaru] That's good.
[Assun] Good. I was worried
- 'cause they cost millions of yen.
- Yeah, for real.
Tell us about your past.
- Like, why are you here?
- My past?
I was married.
Really?
[laughter]
HA-CHAN (27)
TRAINER
[Assun] You said it so casually.
- You don't try to hide it.
- Mmm.
And how long were you married for?
- About six months.
- [Ruru] Okay.
- Yeah.
- [Hikaru] What about kids? You have kids?
No kids?
Okay.
I kind of burned out.
When were you married?
- Yeah, so it was last summer.
- [Ha-chan] Mmm.
- [Assun] Really?
- Around then.
- [Ha-chan] That's recent.
- [Assun] Not that long ago.
- Yeah.
- What's your type?
[Megumi] Ruru really goes for it.
- Girls who are charming.
- Mmm.
It's not about having a pretty face.
Like, I don't care about that anymore.
- I totally get that.
- There's so many pretty girls.
I want a girl who can have fun with me
at a shabby izakaya.
- [all] Mmm.
- I totally get that.
I don't want to be with a girl
who only likes expensive restaurants,
who I have to force myself to be with.
[Nagano] Look at Ruru's eyes.
- Hey, what's your blood type?
- [Kazu-kun] Type O.
- What?
- [women gasp, exclaim]
- Hi, Type O.
- What's this?
[giggles] I'm Type O too.
[Megumi] Ruru thinks
he's pretty attractive, huh?
[Leo sighs]
LEO (25)
BAR OWNER
ARI (AGE 29)
RAPPER/MODEL
"You go make it" is not the way to say it.
- Did he say, "Go make it"?
- Yeah.
"Go make it 'cause you were told to."
The hell? You say "please"
when you ask for something.
Don't skip all the steps, punk.
Washing the rice…
NAGANO
[all laugh]
- [Bo] I'll help out.
- Huh?
- [Bo] I'll help.
- [Ma-kun] You don't have to cook.
- We'll do it today.
- [Ma-kun] Yeah.
- You shouldn't be a burden to your bros.
- [Bo] No.
[Ari] I'll help too.
Ari, Bo, it's okay.
Just don't think you're making it for him.
- [Megumi] So mature.
- Yeah.
- But it's not right to cause you trouble.
- [Leo] This isn't trouble.
[Bo] I'll help.
MA-KUN (28)
MMA FIGHTER
I don't want to make it. [chuckles]
I think if he says thank you,
then I might forgive him,
just a little bit.
- Oh, he won't.
- [Leo] Only if he says thank you.
Hey, why don't we wait
and see what his reaction is?
[Leo] If he says it, we'll forgive him.
But if he says he doesn't want it,
I won't hold back.
[Megumi] Bo is super-efficient though,
with everything he does.
- [Awich] Yeah, that's true.
- [Nagano] Obviously. He did it before.
[Megumi] Right? He's done a lot of things.
- [Maririn] Delivery.
- [Ruru] Bo, are you the waiter?
No, I cooked the rice.
I was always gonna help.
- [Hikaru] Oh, thank you.
- [Ha-chan] Aw.
What's that?
- Pot-au-feu?
- [Ma-kun] Pot-au-feu.
- [Assun] You made pot-au-feu?
- I want to eat it.
- [Assun] I wanted to make pot-au-feu.
- [Ari] It's pot-au-feu, isn't it?
- [Leo] Taisei made it today.
- [Hikaru] Oh, really?
- [Nagano] What's gonna happen?
- [Leo] It's hot.
- [Megumi] What're they gonna do?
- [Hikaru] Smells amazing, guys.
[Megumi] Look how mad he is.
- All right.
- Shall we eat?
- Let's eat.
- [Tai-chan] Yeah.
Thank you, Ma-kun.
Whoa!
[chill music playing]
- [Leo] We made it together.
- Thank you, guys.
[all] Let's eat.
[Nagano] What just happened?
- [Awich laughs] What's happening?
- [Ma-kun] It's good.
- [Ha-chan] Yeah.
- [Ma-kun] It's all right, Ari.
Thanks, Taisei, that was delicious.
- No problem. Did y'all like it?
- [Ma-kun] Yeah.
[Ari] Did y'all like it?
- [Assun] Tamo-san? Like Tamo-san.
- [laughs]
- [Megumi and Awich] He's laughing!
- [Nagano] Wait a minute!
- [laughs]
- Like, what just happened?
They feel what they feel in the moment.
- Just like chickens, right?
- No.
- Take a few steps, and forget.
- They're human.
What you're witnessing
are beautiful yankii hearts.
[opening theme song playing]
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
RAPPER FROM SAGAMIHARA
SPITTING LYRICS OF PURE LOVE
ARI
KAWASAKI'S IT-GIRL HOSTESS
OUT TO FIND A REAL MAN
HIKARU
KYOTO BAR OWNER
GOING ALL-IN FOR HIS WOMAN
NANIWA'S BARROOM BEAUTY
LOOKING FOR TRUE LOVE
MARIRIN
KURUME YANKII
WHO GREW UP BEHIND BARS
BO
EX-YAKUZA MMA FIGHTER
LOOKING FOR HIS RIDE-OR-DIE
MA-KUN
NAGOYA'S NO.1 HOSTESS
WHO PUTS MEN IN THEIR PLACE
ASSUN
FACE-TATTOOED STYLIST
WHO LOVES HARD
TAI-CHAN
AN HONEST MODEL
IN SEARCH OF LOVE
RURU
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON THE LOVE
NO FILTER KICKBOXER
FROM MIYAGI
HA-CHAN
EX-NO.1 HOST
CHASING TRUE LOVE
KAZU-KUN
- [PA system chiming]
- Oh, here it comes.
- It's 'cause you just said that!
- [Ruru] Aren't I amazing?
- [Ha-chan] That's amazing.
- I told you.
- [boy on PA] Everybody, it's sauna time.
- [Ha-chan] Here we go.
- [Assun] Won't be Ari.
- Hikaru.
The person who gets to choose is…
Please be Hikaru.
…the transfer student, Kazu-kun.
[Ari] Why?
- Now?
- [Assun] Yeah, like, right now.
I choose…
Okay.
- [Nagano] Ruru…
- [Megumi] Ooh!
- Shall we?
- Yes.
[Megumi] Of course,
he's been locked on her since the start.
[Nagano] Wow.
[Megumi] He's not putting his bathrobe on.
[Nagano laughs]
You look like
you're feeling pretty refreshed.
- [giggles]
- Huh? Let's go in.
- [Ruru] Wow, it's warm.
- [Awich laughs]
[Megumi] These two look
kind of good together.
[Ruru] This feels good.
So at the moment,
what's the lay of the land like?
What's the situation?
Assun and Ma-kun.
- I see that, yeah.
- Assun is going for Ma-kun.
I was interested in Leo to begin with.
And now?
Well, it's not that I'm not interested,
I just don't know how he feels about me.
So, even when
we talk one-on-one, it's like--
- Nothing happens.
- Exactly, nothing happens.
- Mmm.
- I don't know how he feels about me.
You're not going to make a move?
- I would if I was sure it was love.
- Uh-huh.
But, yeah, I think out of all the guys,
he's the only one I like.
- [Kazu-kun] Mmm.
- I'm interested in him.
I think?
It's like I'm half interested in him
right now.
[laughs] So you're not fully interested.
Right. Because, I mean,
he hasn't made a move either.
- [Kazu-kun] Hmm.
- So I'm like, "What's going on?"
I see.
[Megumi and Nagano laugh]
- [Nagano] Drinking away.
- [Megumi] Meanwhile, Leo…
[Ari] How do you feel right now?
- Well, I'm not happy.
- [Bo] Yeah, figures.
- [Ma-kun] Yeah.
- Yeah.
People have this image of me
as a notorious player…
Uh-huh, yeah.
- …and that image has stuck.
- Yeah. That's the image I have.
[laughs] And we've had
a drink together once before.
- Yeah, we have.
- Yeah, you remember?
I don't remember where exactly,
but I'm sure you were
- in that circle of people.
- Uh-huh, yeah.
Yeah, I thought so.
- [Megumi] They've met before.
- You were right.
Her face looked like they'd met before.
- [Nagano] You were saying that.
- Hmm.
I was surprised when the door opened.
Like, seriously?
- [chuckles]
- I was like, "They chose him?" [chuckles]
- You were on their sign.
- Mm.
I already knew who you were.
I was telling everyone about this host
- who I thought was handsome.
- Oh, wow.
- Are you a fortune-teller?
- [Nagano] Right?
- You keep guessing--
- Are you cheating?
- Have you already seen the footage?
- I'm not cheating. I just…
have detective skills.
Now you're scaring me.
- Another.
- Detective skills?
Huh? You know if someone's lying?
- I can tell when someone's lying.
- Or you can tell what they're thinking?
When it comes to love,
I can tell straight away.
[both] Wow.
- That's reassuring.
- Yeah.
I don't know what Ruru's thinking.
Mmm.
I'm starting to wonder if
she's actually even interested in Leo.
Yeah. She said something like
she's only half-interested in him.
- Like, is that even a real thing?
- [laughs]
I don't think so.
- I mean, is it really that difficult?
- She's half interested.
- [Megumi] It's so intense.
- [Nagano] It's so erotic, like…
- It's like watching porn.
- [Megumi laughs] I get that!
[Awich] But it looks beautiful.
This is just a little tidbit,
but a friend of mine was watching
the last Badly In Love,
he was watching on his phone,
and he was so turned on by it,
that he tried to pinch in it to zoom,
but you can't do that on Netflix.
- [laughing]
- Yeah. He was frustrated.
That makes me happy, he got sucked in.
He kept trying with his finger…
To zoom in on it?
'Cause he was watching on his phone.
He wanted to see the body.
- Poor guy, you can't zoom in on Netflix.
- I'm sorry, my--
- There are fans who are like my friend.
- [Awich] I see.
- [Megumi] Fans of the sauna time.
- Yes.
- [Ha-chan] He has a really handsome face.
- [women laugh]
- I thought he was handsome.
- He has a beautiful face.
ASSUN (30)
ENTREPRENEUR/HOSTESS
Anyone would think he's handsome.
I wanted him to choose me for the sauna.
- [Assun] You did?
- I wanted him to choose me.
[Nagano and Megumi] What?
[Awich] She's honest.
I'm super curious about what you're like
when you fall for somebody
and how you're gonna play things
while you're here at the academy.
- [both laugh]
- I can't imagine it at all.
I'm all or nothing. If I'm not interested
in someone, then there's nothing there.
- Okay, I see.
- Yeah.
[Ruru] All or nothing is way better.
- [Kazu-kun] Right?
- Yeah, definitely better.
- [Assun] Here she comes.
- [all] Welcome back.
- [Assun] How'd it go?
- [Ha-chan] She's got a huge smile.
- [Assun] She looks happy.
- [Ha-chan] What happened?
I think I like sauna time now. It was fun.
- Oh!
- Oh, really?
When I was in there with Ma-kun,
it was a little awkward,
but it wasn't awkward this time.
I already thought he was good-looking,
so I just told him what I thought.
Mmm.
So I told him he's my type
and I think he's good-looking.
- [Assun] Yeah.
- That's what happened.
[Megumi] What's he going to do
in the men's room?
[Leo] I'm not worried.
- Excuse me.
- [Leo] You know?
Hi, guys. Can we talk?
[sighs, grunts]
There was a slight misunderstanding
when I said I didn't want
to be friends with you guys.
And there's no room for romance
when things are awkward like this.
I said it
because I want to find love here.
But if I'm all, like, buddy-buddy,
I have a habit of giving up on the girl
if one of my friends also likes her.
So I said it because I didn't want
to get too friendly with you guys.
But I, low-key,
do want to get along with you.
What do you say?
- [Ma-kun] Sure.
- Yeah.
You just gotta tell us.
- I'm sorry I broke your chain.
- Nah, I'm sorry too.
Was the curry good?
It was, but I was so full
of adrenaline, I couldn't eat.
- Hey, that's exactly what you said.
- I told you, didn't I?
- [Ma-kun] Couldn't taste it, huh?
- [Leo] He said you wouldn't.
I was thinking,
"I can't swallow this. Damn it."
[Megumi] Bo's also smiling. That's good.
- What the…
- They're so adorable.
- No, no, wait.
- Huh?
- I'm the only one who's still mad.
- Right? Me too.
- Right?
- I'm with you.
- You're still mad?
- I'm mad at Kazu-kun's attitude.
- [Megumi] Jeez, you take your time.
- Why'd they forgive him?
You guys were the ones
who stirred it up and made me mad.
He said,
"Thank you for the curry, Ma-kun."
- Isn't that enough?
- So that means you can say anything?
If you feel that something's off,
you can't move on?
Uh, that's right.
- You've been with us since Season 1.
- [Nagano] Yes.
I'd like you
to not come back to this every time.
- I'd also like that.
- Let's do our best.
I think a lot of viewers
will be feeling the same.
Like some middle-aged man
watching Badly In Love really furious.
[Megumi] That's true.
LOVE DINER
- [Hikaru] Are there more dishes to clean?
- [Bo] Tai-chan brought some.
[Leo] Yeah, I don't mind, though.
MARIRIN (25)
BAR WORKER
You know, Bo, I got pushed real hard,
when you beat him up.
- I got pushed really hard.
- Oh, yeah?
[Maririn] Yeah.
And I was like, "Oh, yeah? Seriously?"
[Nagano] "Yeah, seriously"?
[Megumi] Well, she found out
that Bo raised his hand to a girl, so…
[Nagano] Oh, I see.
Violence is scary, for sure.
[Megumi] Yeah.
Hey, Maririn.
- Hey, thanks for coming.
- [Ma-kun] No problem.
So, Maririn was talking to me earlier on,
- and it was about Bo.
- Yeah.
I think Maririn's main issue
is trying to overcome her past trauma.
That's the biggest thing.
She can't fall in love.
So Bo, Maririn, Ruru, and Leo
were all talking together.
- [Maririn] Yeah.
- [Ma-kun] Mmm.
And during the conversation, Bo mentioned
that he has hit a woman before.
Yeah, he said he hit a woman.
What?
So that conversation happened,
and then you know
how he hit the transfer student?
[Ma-kun] Uh-huh. Yeah.
- I got pushed really hard.
- [Ma-kun] Yeah.
And while we were doing the dishes,
I told him I got pushed,
and he was like, "Oh, yeah?"
And I was like, "Oh, so that's how it is."
And I wanted to say something back,
you know, like,
"Aren't you going to apologize?"
But I was scared he might hit me.
So I didn't.
- Let's talk to him.
- [Maririn] Yeah.
- Yeah. I'll get him.
- [Assun] Okay.
- [Maririn] Yeah.
- If there's any bad blood, then…
- Yeah.
- [Awich] He's showing his strength.
[Megumi] That's Ma-kun.
[Ma-kun] Do you remember
what Maririn said?
- How she was abused by her ex-boyfriend?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
[Ma-kun] Girls are scared of that.
Guys are stronger than girls.
Mmm-hmm.
[Ma-kun] Right?
And earlier, you slammed into her.
Mmm-hmm.
- When you were fighting with Kazuma.
- Oh, sorry about that.
But you didn't apologize earlier.
Oh, sorry about that.
I wasn't considerate enough.
- Sorry.
- Yeah.
It's okay.
Cheating is definitely not okay.
- Definitely.
- Hmm, yeah.
No matter how you look at it.
But guys…
should never hit girls.
- Never.
- [Ma-kun] They're not as strong as us.
- We shouldn't do it.
- [Ma-kun] Yeah.
Do you promise not to hit a woman?
Yeah, I promise.
- Thank you for talking to me.
- Now make peace.
- I mean--
- Let's make peace.
- Wow, you can spread your legs super wide.
- [laughing]
- Never seen that.
- [Assun] Your hips are flexible.
[Ma-kun] Bo's such a yankii,
know what I mean?
- Sorry.
- [Maririn] No worries.
[Megumi] I'm so glad.
[PA system chiming]
[boy on PA] So, today's Valentine's Day.
- I forgot about it.
- They're telling us.
[boy on PA] A day
for expressing love and gratitude
to your partner
or someone important to you.
Gentlemen, your task
is to prepare a homemade box of candy
to let the woman you're interested in
know exactly how you feel about her.
- Task understood.
- [Ma-kun] All right!
- Let's do this! Come on!
- Wassup!
Let's go!
[Megumi] What the heck?
They were fighting just a second ago.
[Ma-kun] Wow!
[romantic music playing]
- [Nagano] He's so dexterous.
- [Megumi] Bo's drawing a heart.
[Ari] This would be better
with white chocolate.
I didn't know this was what
giving candy feels like.
TAISEI
SUCH AN ANGEL
- [Nagano] Wow. Tai-chan.
- [Megumi] Oh, my.
TAI-CHAN'S CREATION
- [Megumi] Their personalities are showing.
- [Nagano] So cute.
MA-KUN'S CREATION
KAZU-KUN'S CREATION
BO'S CREATION
[Nagano] Bo.
- [Awich] Bo's is adorable.
- [Megumi] So lovely.
- [Nagano] Cute.
- [Awich] It's badass.
- [Megumi] He's done fruit!
- [Nagano chuckles]
- [Megumi] Nice.
- [Nagano] Nice.
ARI'S CREATION
TO RURU
HAPPY BALEN
It's a "T-A." Cross out the "N."
- "N-N-T…"?
- "N-N-T-A."
"N"? "Valentine"?
- Yo, you're useless!
- [Ma-kun laughs]
Don't bother.
Hey, hold on.
If I'm useless, then so's he.
"Ba-re-."
Like I'm typing on the computer.
Bro, you're using romaji!
- Didn't you say romaji?
- That just sounds out the words!
- [both laughing]
- Come on, bro! Seriously, what the hell?
Like, who the hell would do that?
Why would I write it out in romaji?
Huh? Idiot!
[Awich] They're having fun.
[Leo] I asked for the spelling in English!
[laughing]
This kind of thing is always the most fun.
- Right?
- [Nagano] Yeah.
LEO'S CREATION
[Nagano] He's good.
- [Awich] Leo's good at this.
- [Megumi] Leo is really good.
- [Awich] He might be the best.
- [Megumi] Wow.
I think the chocolates Kazuma made
will be really good.
You want 'em. [laughs]
[Maririn] She does.
- I bet Kazuma's will be really good.
- Hmm, Leo's might be better.
You think so?
[boy on PA] When you have finished,
please go to the office
and call the person you like
over the PA system.
[PA system chimes]
BROADCASTING
It's Ma-kun.
My box of candy is for…
Assun.
[Nagano] Well, yeah.
[Ma-kun] Please, come to the sauna room.
- The sauna room?
- [Ruru] What?
- Finally! Nice.
- [Ruru] Have fun!
But we're not going to go
in the sauna, are we?
[chimes]
[man over PA system] One two, one two.
- Who's that?
- Is it Kazuma?
- It's Tai-chan.
- Uh, it's Tai-chan.
[Ha-chan chuckling] Oh, no.
[Megumi] Who will Tai-chan pick?
My box of candy is for…
Hikaru.
I'll be in the smoking area
in the courtyard.
[Assun] He just wanted to smoke,
so he picked there.
- [laughs]
- [Nagano] Well, yeah.
[Megumi] She looks like
she's really mad at him.
[chimes]
[Bo] My Valentine's Day candy is for…
- [Ruru] That's cute.
- [giggles]
…Hikaru.
[Nagano] She's popular.
Look at you acting all surprised.
No, I really am.
I didn't know Bo would do that.
[chimes]
[Ari] Yo! Mic check,
one, two, one, two!
- Wassup!
- [laughing]
Uh, it's Ari, uh…
The woman I want to give
my chocolates to is…
Hikaru!
- [Ruru] This is so amazing.
- I want to give them to her…
- It's just like, bravo, girl.
- …uh, even though I…
I wasn't very good at it.
- I made some chocolates…
- [Ruru] So cute.
…with a lot of love.
[Ruru] So cute.
So I'll be waiting in the kitchen.
Please come!
- That's nice.
- He said it the best.
[Kazu-kun] That was nice.
It's Leo here.
I want to give my box of candy…
to Ruru.
- [Nagano] Devoted.
- [Megumi] Since day one.
[Leo] I made them with all my love.
I'll be waiting behind the gymnasium.
See you there.
- [laughing]
- [Hikaru] I think he wants to grill you.
He wants to grill you about the fact that
you went to the sauna with Kazuma.
- He's gonna make me dogeza.
- [Megumi] What potty mouths.
- [Nagano laughs]
- Hi. It's Kazu-kun.
[Hikaru] It's Kazu-kun.
Uh, I want to give my box of candy…
to Ruru.
[Hikaru and Ha-chan] Oh.
- [Hikaru] She's happy.
- Please come to the living room.
- Is it the usual?
- [Hikaru] She's so happy.
- [Ruru] Did he say the living room?
- [Nagano] Oh, no.
Well, well, well. [laughs]
Okay, I'm off.
- [all] Have fun.
- Enjoy.
I'll wear Masaya's jacket.
[Ruru] Be careful.
- I'm going.
- [Ruru] See you later.
- Thank you.
- I've never made candy before.
- Yeah, I've never been gifted them either.
- [laughs]
- So you made them?
- I made them.
- It's kind of--
- This is so cute, I love the heart.
- I felt embarrassed making it.
- [both laugh]
Seriously.
This is the first time in my life
that I've received a handmade gift.
[laughs]
It's so cute!
- Dang!
- [Ma-kun] I'm glad you like it.
[Assun giggles] So did you,
like, decorate it all yourself?
- [Ma-kun] I did.
- [Assun] That's so cute.
I thought they'd be the least fattening.
- Strawberries?
- Strawberries.
- Can I eat one?
- Go ahead.
- Okay, then. Thank you.
- Mmm.
Mmm.
Mmm, it's good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
They seem comfortable together.
It's a strong bond.
- [Nagano] I know.
- I feel like it is.
- Like an old married couple.
- [both] Yeah.
And they even have a similar tone.
- Look good together.
- [Megumi] They do.
[boy on PA] You are now going to accept
the men's offers of love.
For the ones who received multiple offers
from different men,
you will accept the offers
in the order corresponding
to your own feelings.
I can't decide.
- [Ha-chan] You can't?
- [Hikaru] Right?
[pensive music playing]
Which order are you going in?
Oh, what should I do?
[Megumi] That's a luxury problem.
You don't usually get this kind of choice.
- I'm going.
- [Ruru] Hope it goes well.
- [Ha-chan] Bye.
- [Ruru] See you.
Maybe I'll try being
a little more aggressive.
- I can't go on like this.
- Yeah.
[Megumi] Who will Hikaru go to first?
[gasps softly]
- [Awich] Huh?
- [Nagano] What?
[Megumi] She just walked straight past him
and went somewhere else.
- Wassup, man?
[chuckles] Wassup, man?
- [Nagano] Well, that's unexpected.
- Hey.
- Have a seat.
- [exhales]
- Hey. Am I the first?
- Mmm-hmm.
Oh, I see.
I made this.
- Thank you.
- Yes, to Hikaru.
I made this for you.
I thought you might be on a diet,
so I made sure it was mostly fruit.
- Oh, really?
- I thought you might not want chocolate.
So I thought that if it was all
just chocolate, it might be too much.
Why am I the first?
I thought about it a lot,
and out of everybody
who's been expressing their feelings…
Yeah.
…you've been
expressing your feelings to me the most.
Wow! You're a genius.
- [Ari] Right?
- Yeah.
[Ari] Wasn't sure if you'd like it
'cause it's chocolate.
[Hikaru] It's really good.
- Yum!
- Is it good? You like it?
Here.
- Thank you.
I'm so happy you came to me first.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Let's shake hands.
- Wassup, man?
- Yeah, I feel you.
[Nagano] I like his honesty.
- [Awich] Yeah.
- [Nagano] He says what he thinks.
[Megumi] Adorable.
- [Nagano laughs] That's so adorable.
- [Megumi] Aw, that's cute.
- So cute!
- [Nagano] Like in Platoon.
- Awesome!
- [Nagano laughs]
I've never seen anyone do that except
for when they score a goal in soccer.
- Now you have.
- It looks exactly like that.
- [Hikaru] Sorry to keep you waiting.
- [Tai-chan] Happy Valentine's Day.
Happy Valentine's Day.
I've never done this before,
but I'd like to give you some candy.
Thank you. [gasps] What a cute bag.
I'm glad you like it.
I realized when I made it
that you won't be able to eat it all.
- Why not?
- There's a lot in there.
Huh? Oh my god, wait.
- This is so cute!
- You can take it out.
- You have crazy good taste.
- Right?
I've got good taste in everything.
It's so cute! I want to display it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You've really changed for real.
- What do you mean?
- I mean, I can tell.
- Which means?
At first, I thought you were such a sissy.
[Tai-chan] Mmm.
But now when I see you talking
to all of the other guys in here,
like, I think,
"Oh, he's definitely a guy."
- You think that, do you?
- Yeah.
- For real? Well, I'm glad you can tell.
- Mmm-hmm.
Good night then.
- Good night. Thanks.
- I feel better.
- [Hikaru] Thank you. Thank you.
- Good night.
Cute.
I can't confess my feelings yet, can I?
- [Bo] Here.
- [Hikaru] Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh, here you go.
- Thank you.
- It's not the best, but…
Oh! That's cute.
I never would have thought
that you'd make something
like this, Bo, like, seriously.
It's cute.
You've taken me by surprise.
- Huh?
- By surprise.
[both chuckle]
I guess that the girl
who I like the most is you, Hikaru.
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
- The order was Ari, Tai, then Bo.
- Hmm. Mmm.
And that's because
you're still the one
I know the least about.
- That's true. You don't really know much.
- Let's talk.
To be honest,
when I heard that you had
raised a hand to a girl before,
I was like, "What?!"
Mmm.
- Like, "Bou, really?"
- Mmm.
I wanted people to know about me.
And so I talked about it, even though
I thought it would be negative.
- Mmm.
- The negative part of me.
- That's also part of who I am.
- Mmm.
And because I told them,
I now see things differently.
- Mmm.
- Now, I really strongly believe that
- I should never hit a girl ever again.
- Mmm.
It was bad that I hit her,
but I see things differently now
because of that experience.
Mmm.
Yeah. That's how it is.
- I'm going!
- [Maririn] Bye.
[Megumi] Ruru…
How can she be so happy
in front of these two?
- [laughs] Yeah, I know.
- Yeah, you're absolutely right.
- That's true.
- That's what's amazing.
- [Awich] It really is.
- About Ruru.
[Nagano] Which one will she go to?
- Hey. [giggles]
- [Nagano] What?
- Hey.
- [Ruru] Hey.
- This is for you.
- Thank you! Yay!
What? This is so cute.
This is the first time
I've ever made candy.
- [laughs]
- For real.
Oh, it's so cute!
- You're good at it.
- No way.
[Ruru] It's so cute.
Mmm! It's good.
Marshmallow?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Mmm! It's good.
I thought there was a chance
you wouldn't come to me first.
- Mmm.
- It's my first day.
I was like, "Damn" and then, "Oh, well,
it can't be helped,
but it's pretty tough."
- Right.
- Yeah.
- I'm glad I was first.
- Yeah?
[sighs]
[Megumi] Oh, Leo.
Well, this is nice.
What are you giving me?
Well, I'd like us to spend
more time talking together.
- Let's talk.
- Yeah.
- So stay near me then.
- [Nagano] Oh.
- Take action.
- [Megumi] Oh, my.
- Okay.
- Then we'll be able to talk a lot.
- True.
- [Ruru] Hey!
- Hey.
- [giggles] Aren't you cold?
- I am.
- It's cold!
- You've already got one.
I intentionally saved you for last
'cause I wanted to talk.
- Really?
- Yeah. I did it on purpose.
- Ooh-ooh!
- Hello!
Wow, this girl.
- [Nagano] Scary.
- [Megumi] "This girl."
- Ruru, Awich is angry.
- [Nagano] Detective!
- [Ruru chuckles]
- For real?
- For real, yeah.
- Oh, okay.
I had a short and simple conversation
with him.
But I wanted to talk to you properly, so…
I wanted to yesterday, but we couldn't.
I wanted to spend more time with you,
so I saved you for last.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Thank you for waiting.
- [Ruru] Oh my god. That's amazing!
- I made it with love.
- Please accept it.
- Thank you. Wow, amazing!
Wow, it's so… wow! It's so cute!
- [Leo] I wanted to make a toy poodle.
- I see.
[Leo] But I just couldn't picture
a toy poodle in my head.
[Ruru laughs] I'll eat it later.
- [Leo] Okay.
- In our room.
I mean, you and I
do spend a lot of time together,
but we haven't really
talked about our feelings.
I was thinking the same thing.
That's why I've been thinking I want
to tell you that I feel like I have to…
- just say it.
- Or we can't move forward.
- Exactly.
- Yeah, I've been thinking the same thing.
- So the way I feel about you is…
- Yeah?
I'm interested in you.
And I know you're also interested in me,
but you're not, like,
expressing it or putting it into words.
So, for me, it's like,
what are you actually thinking?
To be honest…
whether it's the dates, the meals,
or the one-on-ones,
I'd only choose you, Ruru.
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
And…
I want to be with you all the time.
Like, when I saw the transfer student,
- Kazu, sitting next to you…
- Yeah?
[Leo] …I was like,
"What the hell is this guy doing?"
[Ruru] Mmm.
I want to date somebody
who I can think about the future with.
- You're mainly in Kyoto, right?
- Mmm-hmm.
And I'm in Tokyo.
So we're both working in different places.
- So we'd be long-distance.
- Yeah.
- Tokyo, here I come.
- [laughs] That's my main concern.
- We'll cross that bridge later on.
- Yeah, you're right.
I really like you right now.
[romantic music playing]
I don't know what to say,
I just know that I like you.
[laughing] But I genuinely believe
your honesty, Leo.
Thank you.
- See you tomorrow.
- [Leo] Good night.
- [Nagano and Megumi] Aw.
- Good night. Thank you.
Guess I'm moving to Tokyo.
[Awich] Leo is adorable.
Okay, wait, so what
do you guys think about Ruru?
Detective, what do you think?
[inhales sharply] Stay away from her.
[laughs] Yeah,
that's what you wanted to say.
- [Megumi] I mean, to put it simply, yeah.
- So you say, "Stay away from her."
Kazu-kun and Ruru, they're a good match,
in a way, you know?
- Uh-huh, 'cause Kazu-kun is popular.
- [Nagano] Popular.
- I mean, both of them…
- They flirt with each other.
- Yeah, kind of.
- I see.
It's like Kazu-kun and Ruru
are playing cards with words.
"This is the first time
I've ever made candy for a girl."
"I want to be with you,
so stay close to me."
I mean, they're exchanging techniques.
- For sure.
- It's like a duel.
Nothing but techniques,
rather than real words.
[Megumi] Yeah.
She's probably
not thinking too much about it,
she's just following her instincts.
"I want to have romance with this person."
"But with this person,
I want to be serious and find out more."
- Yeah, like thinking about the future.
- Maybe that's what she's thinking.
Because she didn't say anything
about the future to Kazu-kun.
[Nagano] She didn't.
But then again, it could also just be that
she's keeping Leo as a backup
in case Kazu-kun turns her down.
- [Nagano] Oh, you think so?
- It could be a simple strategy like that.
- Huh. Gosh.
- Oh, look, I don't know anymore.
It seems us three
are the ones getting played by Ruru.
It's like we're trying to read
the mind of a criminal.
This whole time,
we've been treating Ruru like a criminal.
- [both laughing]
- For some reason.
- [thudding]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [Ma-kun] Rock or paper.
- [both] Okay.
- [Nagano] This is…
- [Megumi] A hundred percent tattooed.
[Awich laughs]
[Nagano] It looks like
a prison lunch break.
- [Megumi laughs]
- [Awich] So cool.
[Ma-kun whoops]
[both yell]
[rap music playing]
[laughter]
[Ruru] Hey, stop it. For real.
Don't make me laugh.
Wait, mine's the green one, isn't it?
- [Assun] Let's go in.
- [Leo] Good morning.
[Ari] Good morning.
I see that you're wearing all black today.
But to me you're pure white,
'cause you're--
- Morning.
[laughs]
[Megumi] Guys who say things like that
are adorable.
- [PA system chiming]
- [Ha-chan] Here we go.
[boy on PA] Today,
somebody will get to go on a date.
- [Ma-kun] Yes!
- [Tai-chan] All right!
The guys are
going to have to battle it out.
[boy on PA] And that somebody
is the person who received
the most Valentine's Day candy.
Hikaru.
- [Leo] Ooh.
- Aw, that sucks.
- I would've won if I got two more.
- [laughter]
[boy on PA] Hikaru,
you are going on a date
with all of the guys
who gave you a box of candy.
- [Assun] All of them?
- Really?
- [Kazu-kun] All of them?
- Huh? Say what?
- You're going with all three.
- [Ha-chan] That's nice.
- Wow, okay.
- [Leo] Uh-huh.
- [Tai-chan] All four of us?
- [Assun] A reverse harem.
[Megumi and Nagano]
This is gonna be tough.
- [Megumi] Gonna be hell.
- How'll she handle this?
They're going to find out
how she acts around their rivals.
- [Nagano] She'll be exposed.
- Yeah.
- Wow, what is this place?
- It's Ryukyu Mura.
Ryukyu! Ryukyu. Wassup shisa!
RYUKYU VILLAGE
- This is so Okinawa.
- This is crazy.
- Oh, wow.
- [Nagano] Don't run.
- [Megumi] They're like kids.
- [Nagano] Shouldn't run in those clothes.
- [yelps]
- You okay?
Yeah. My foot nearly slipped.
Careful. Careful.
[Ari] There's something
for four people here.
[Tai-chan] We drawing a shisa? Okay.
- [Hikaru] Oh! These?
- [Tai-chan] This is what we're painting?
- Looks like we're painting them.
- [Hikaru] Okay, let's decorate the shisa.
If you look at them front on,
the one on the right is the male.
And the female is on the left,
they're a pair.
Why don't we choose
who paints the shisa out of us.
- Hikaru decides.
- Okay.
- [Tai-chan] Go with your gut.
[pleasant music playing]
[laughs] That's your personality
showing through, right?
- That's my personality all over.
- [Hikaru] That's awesome.
- [Ari] Better than Picasso.
- [Hikaru laughs]
[Ari] Isn't it cool?
- [Tai-chan] The theme is anger.
- [Nagano] Awesome.
[Megumi] Tai-chan's so good
with his hands.
[Ari] The theme is
"my feelings for Hikaru."
- I put them into colors.
- [Hikaru] So it's random?
[Ari] It's not random. [laughs]
- [Bo] They're my favorite colors.
- [Tai-chan] Oh, I see.
- [Awich] What a craftsman.
- [Tai-chan] Yellow and green.
- That's the work of a 60-year-old man.
- [laughing]
Really. I mean,
it's like the work of somebody
who's just found out
about the art of subtraction.
It's like, "In the end,
it's better not to paint."
Yeah, it's like…
It's like his 10,000th piece of work.
- Yeah, his 10,000th shisa!
- [laughing]
The title is so profound too,
"My Favorite Colors".
- That's true.
- Exactly.
[Nagano] "My Favorite Colors" makes you
wonder about so many different things.
- "My Favorite Colors." [laughing]
- [Nagano] This is too much subtraction.
[Tai-chan] Which one do you feel
has the best set of aesthetics?
- [Bo] This one.
- The one I thought was the cutest was…
Tai-chan's.
Why, thank you. Thank you.
But, hey, there's no, like,
deeper meaning to it.
- Aesthetically, it's Tai-chan's.
- Can I smash this up?
It's pissing me off.
- [Hikaru chuckles]
- [Ari] Just kidding.
[boy on PA] There is a nearby banana farm,
which is in need of some young helpers.
The remaining members, please go
down to the banana farm to help out.
- Good morning.
- How are you?
- [Assun] Hello.
- [Leo] Hello.
MR. HENTONA
- Yes, welcome.
- Hello, sir.
[Hentona chuckles]
- [Kazu-kun] He's like the final boss.
- [all laugh]
[Ha-chan] Like Dragon Quest.
[Hentona] You all have such good faces.
Nice to meet you. You're strong.
- I can give the guys a hug.
- [Maririn] Aw.
So you'll be sure to come back again.
- Yes, sir.
- Who's the leader?
- Go ahead.
- I am.
Here you are.
- [Leo] Mr. Hentona.
- Yes.
"Mr. Hentona is known for…"
- What's that?
- Bashofu.
…"transforming a village
which was once the home of bashofu,"
"Ogimi village."
- [Assun] Damn.
- Hmm?
- Why don't you read?
- Get him to read it.
You read.
"He is a man
who has dedicated his life to bananas,
transforming Ogimi
back to the home of bananas."
[Assun] Wow.
[boy on PA] He spent ten years creating
an entire banana farm all by himself.
[Nagano] That's amazing.
[boy on PA] Please make sure you work hard
for Mr. Hentona today.
[relaxing music playing]
This is a high-class banana.
They're so good you can eat the skin.
- That's what we have here.
- [Ruru] Wow.
- [Ma-kun] Whoa!
- [Ruru] You can eat the skin?
Wow. Let's go.
- [Hentona] Remove these.
- [Ha-chan] Dead ones?
[Hentona] Remove the dead leaves.
[Ruru] Mr. Hentona, how did you create
this field of banana trees?
- At first, it was a forest like that.
- [Ruru] Really?
It was a really dense forest.
And I used a power shovel
to knock down the trees.
- Uh-huh.
- And then I mowed the grass.
- [Ruru] By yourself?
- By myself.
- [Ruru] Just you?
- Just me.
- [Maririn] That's crazy.
- [Ruru] That's insane!
[Hentona] 3.2 acres, four locations.
- [Ruru] All by yourself, right?
- [Hentona] By myself.
- And you work on 5,000 trees by yourself?
- [Hentona] I do it every day.
- What? Do you sleep? Do you sleep?
- [Hentona] Huh? I sleep.
But every day, there's stuff to do,
and I gotta mow the grass too.
- [Ha-chan] You're a farmer.
- Right.
- Must be super tough.
- [Ruru] Yeah.
- Just one step at a time.
- [Ha-chan] Right.
[Maririn] Takes time to grow.
No one grows up overnight,
or gets stronger overnight.
- [Ha-chan] That's true.
- Yeah. Everyone starts off weak.
- Wow, that hit me deep.
- That was really deep.
- [Ruru] Really.
- [Hentona] Hang in there.
"Hang in there" hit me too.
I want his number so I can call him
every day, to ask for advice.
- I'll tell you later.
- [laughing]
- [Maririn] Oh, man.
- [Ruru] I want him to tell me.
You boys seem to have a lot of stamina.
- Digging a hole sound good?
- Yes, sir.
- [chuckles] It looks hard.
- [laughs]
- [Nagano] It's like an escape tunnel.
- [Megumi laughs]
[Nagano] Is this an escape attempt?
The security guys need to catch them.
- [Megumi] That's not happening.
- It's hot.
This is tough.
[Hentona] Three a day.
One meter by one meter by one meter.
Over the past four years,
I've dug 500 holes, just like these.
- Five hundred?
- Five hundred.
This is what I do every day.
Super early.
We're halfway there.
- [Hentona] Halfway?
- Yeah.
- Fifty centimeters?
- Yeah, we're there.
- You've worked hard.
- [Nagano] Kazu-kun's doing great.
- [Megumi] Kazu-kun does his share of work.
So do all you guys
have construction experience?
- Yes, in scaffolding. I was a scaffolder.
- A scaffolder.
I did paving. Asphalt.
Oh, okay, yeah.
Kazuma's the same as me,
used to be a scaffolder.
- Oh, as well? I see.
- Yes.
- You did demolition, right, Asuka?
- Uh-huh.
- [Ma-kun] Really?
- Really.
- [Ma-kun] Bingo.
- It was amazing.
[Leo] All right.
[Hentona] We're gonna plant a banana tree
here to commemorate everybody here.
- [Ma-kun] Nice.
- [Leo] All right!
- It's born. [laughs]
- [Maririn] Oh, wow.
- All right!
- That was so cool.
[Assun] You did a great job.
- [all] Ooh!
- [Ma-kun] Nice.
- All right, we're done.
- Okay.
- You worked hard today.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
- [Leo] Joto banana?
- [Ma-kun] Joto banana.
- [Ruru] We're calling it Joto Banana?
- [Ma-kun] You don't like the name?
[Ruru] It's good.
- Let's eat!
- Let's eat.
- [Hentona] High-class banana.
- [Maririn] It's delicious.
- I have 13 varieties at the farm.
- [Ha-chan] So tasty.
[Hentona] Apple banana,
ice-cream banana, Namwa banana.
- This is the legendary banana.
- [Ruru] Huh?
Is that the one you can only get here?
- [Hentona] Exactly.
- [Maririn] You taste that?
- This is good.
- [Assun] I want to try that one.
- [Ma-kun] This is so good.
- [Hentona] This one here.
[Hentona] I think that
being a yankii builds grit.
Especially for boys.
It builds courage.
I was in a biker gang before.
I was in a biker gang in the 1980s.
I was a troublemaker like you
when I was young.
Our gang had 1,000 members.
- You were?
- [Hentona] Right.
Yeah, I was a troublemaker like you
when I was young,
always getting into fights
and doing whatever I wanted.
But nothing comes from fighting.
In the end, love is always stronger.
I'll be straight with you.
The kindest man is the coolest.
And you must never be violent
toward women. You understand?
There's nothing worse. Okay?
Hitting a woman
is the worst thing you can do.
A man like that needs a lot more training.
Bring him to me, I'll knock him out.
- [Nagano] He's so cool.
- [Megumi] Yeah.
- Can I come back again?
- [Hentona] Come back anytime. Anytime.
Really. If you loved it here, come back.
It seems people were more violent
in the past.
Like in the Showa era.
So it's cool that
he's saying things like that anyway.
He said we could come back anytime.
I don't have a home to go back to,
so it made me really happy.
I want to see him again.
He gives me good energy.
- Has she fallen in love with him?
- [Megumi] Fallen in love…
[laughing] Wait a minute.
Do we have another participant?
- Yes.
- Someone of his age?
- A transfer student.
- [Megumi] We have a transfer student.
She really opened up to Mr. Hentona.
Is there a possibility
of her going for Mr. Hentona?
- [laughing] I don't know.
- [Nagano] Like…
I thought this was just them
spending time on a banana farm.
I thought he was just meant
to be a nice uncle.
- Don't let your guard down.
- [Awich] Mmm.
- Can't help let your guard down with him.
- Don't let your guard down, Nagano.
This is Badly in Love!
I really don't want to see Mr. Hentona
bringing his male energy.
We might end up seeing Mr. Hentona
in the sauna.
- We might.
- [Nagano] Mr. Hentona's--
We might.
[mimics boy's voice] "It's sauna time."
[Nagano] "Sauna time," and?
"The person
who worked the hardest, Mr. Hentona."
- [all laugh]
- "Mr. Hentona."
[Tai-chan] Hello. Nice to meet you.
[Hikaru] It's so cute!
What is this, like a park?
[relaxing music playing]
[Tai-chan] Wow.
Say, "Wassup."
- Finally, we got it.
- [Bo] Finally.
Wow, this is actually fun.
Whoa-ho-ho.
It's so much fun.
[laughs]
[Ari] It's really difficult.
- I mean, like, my love for you.
- [Hikaru] Mmm.
I feel like it's not getting through.
I keep asking you questions like,
"How are you?"
"Are you interested in anybody?"
[Hikaru] Mmm.
And when I ask you those things,
you're always like, "No,
I'm not interested in anybody yet."
But you have to be interested in somebody
before you start liking them, right?
You know, we're already
halfway through our time here,
and you tell me you're still
not interested in anybody, so I'm like…
I feel like it's going to drag on,
and we'll run out of time.
You know, like, am I making
any progress with you?
- [Hikaru] Mmm.
- I'm starting to feel anxious.
[Hikaru] So, honestly,
literally, just yesterday,
I made up my mind and decided
to focus only on you
and Tai-chan going forward.
Mmm-hmm.
And I do have a reason for that.
I found out about the time
that Bo hit a girl.
I don't think you can come back from that.
That was a dealbreaker for me,
so I knew I wasn't gonna go for Bo.
And I was planning on
telling him that today.
Well, I'm glad to hear
that you're going to focus on us two,
and that you might turn down Bo
and consider me and Taisei.
I'm happy to hear that.
[Bo] Hey.
- What's up?
- You two should talk.
I've got an iced tea with my name on it.
[Bo chuckles] Okay. What's up?
[Hikaru] Well,
we're halfway through, aren't we?
- [Bo] Yeah, we are.
- [Hikaru] Right.
[Nagano] Is she gonna do it?
Well, when it comes to you,
I was planning on telling you,
or, actually asking you
about something today.
- You were? Okay.
- Mmm-hmm.
I heard that you have hit a woman before.
Mmm.
So, my dad was
really, really abusive towards me.
- He wouldn't hit me 'cause I'd been bad--
- He'd just do it randomly?
He'd hit me if I didn't give him a massage
when he told me to.
Unreasonable.
And so, for me,
no matter what the girl did,
I think that I just couldn't…
be with a guy who'd ever hit a girl.
Mmm.
And so, as of yesterday,
I thought I couldn't be with you.
But today…
All four of us went out together.
And, like, you know…
Now all I can see
is the positive side of you.
- [Nagano] What?
- And I think that you're really…
- You have really good qualities.
- Mmm.
And you actually have good qualities
that neither Ari nor Tai-chan has.
Hmm.
I thought you were going to turn me down.
- I just wanted to make it clear.
- Hmm.
I just wanted to be very clear.
- She's stringing him along.
- [Megumi] Hmm.
Huh? That's totally different
to what she said to Ari.
You know they'll find out later?
I won't be able to know everything
about your past.
I mean, you are similar in a way, but…
[Tai-chan] Not yet?
- [gasps] Whoa.
- More time?
- You scared me.
- Not enough time.
- Not enough?
- No, like, not enough time overall.
- I want us to talk too.
- Mm-hmm.
[Bo] Thanks.
I'm going to tell each of you
what I think about you.
Oh, okay, okay, lay it on me.
- All of you have your flaws.
- Uh-huh. I get that.
And all of you have
your own good qualities.
- Yeah, okay.
- Like, naturally.
I already told Ari this but…
[Tai-chan] Uh-huh.
…I feel like we would just be friends.
Okay, I see.
As for Bo, the domestic violence thing
really bothers me.
- Oh, I heard a bit about that.
- Yeah, it bothers me.
And when it comes to you, Tai-chan…
- Oh, finally.
- [chuckles] Finally, huh?
Finally, my turn.
- Finally…
- Yeah.
- You're like, really mellow, you know?
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, you're quite soft-spoken.
- I am?
Mm-hmm. And I didn't like that.
- Oh, I see.
- But that went away.
That's not how I am.
- And so, now, since that went away…
- Mmm.
So, mmm…
I see you as the one
who's most like a man.
[Nagano] What?
- [giggles]
- What's that?
I see you as the one
who's most like a man.
I thought so. I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
- But honestly…
- [Hikaru] But, like, mm…
Honestly, thank you for that.
And I think you're also
totally my type, looks-wise.
- Who, me?
- Your clothes.
Oh, really?
When I see you with your guy friends,
I just think you seem really cool.
- Like, when you're laughing.
- Yeah, I am cool.
- Yeah.
- Like Ari, he's so loud.
- [laughs]
- I can't understand what he's saying.
Hikaru!
[Tai-chan] I'm glad you've been
so straightforward with me.
I didn't want
to make you talk for too long
'cause that might make you tired,
and I wanted to hear your honest opinion.
I don't know, I'm pretty stoked.
I always knew that I would beat the others
and win you in the end.
- I really did.
- [giggles]
I knew it all along.
So it's me, after all.
This is where I want to hear
the detective's opinion.
Why do you think Hikaru
said those things to the three of them?
What do you think she's thinking?
Well, being popular,
- it feels good, doesn't it?
- [Nagano] It does feel good.
- And she's the most popular.
- [Nagano] Yeah.
So she's probably hoping and trying to
keep this going for as long as possible.
I see.
But if she keeps doing that,
she's going to pay for it later on.
- Right?
- [Megumi] Right.
- [Ma-kun] Let's go have a smoke.
- [Assun] Let's go.
I'm so scared about checking
my phone after all this is over.
[Ma-kun] Me too. I feel the same way.
Reality is going to hit us,
like, super hard.
Yeah. But that's what helped me
make up my mind just now.
I'm gonna be with you.
Be with me?
- No matter what.
- Wanna kiss?
- [Nagano] What?
- [Megumi] Oh!
Won't they expel us?
- Yeah.
- [both laugh]
[clears throat] I mean,
I've never really trusted people,
not really,
- 'cause I'm scared of getting betrayed.
- Mmm-hmm.
But I don't mind it if you do it.
I wanna experience it.
Betrayal.
- You're really saying that?
- Yeah.
Because I honestly don't know.
You're leaving it up to me?
No, it's not that.
- I'm just saying--
- But I've been sharing…
my feelings for you, and you just…
I made a mistake.
Yeah, I don't deserve
to be told that in an angry tone.
I've been more…
I've been more upfront than you
about my feelings.
Forget what I just said. I made a mistake.
[Assun] After the first letter,
it's basically been one-sided on my part.
He hasn't made as much effort.
I sent him a letter,
and I won the girls' competition
and chose him and went on a date.
So if he keeps, like, not reciprocating,
if he doesn't show me any affection,
then I'll be like…
maybe I should just give up on it.
We feel like you want
to keep both of us around.
That's the one thing I didn't want.
And what we're saying is that
that's what it looks like.
- [Nagano] What?
- [Megumi] Oh, my.
[sobbing]
- Wait, no. What? What's going on?
- [Megumi] Oh, no.
Would you cry that much?
Wait, hold on, what was that at the end?
Maybe Mr. Hentona appeared or something?
- [gasps]
- Maybe he was really scared.
- All like, "I'm so scared!" and crying?
- [Nagano] He's like, "I'm so scared!"
- You suck at watching dating shows.
- [all laughing]
[closing theme song playing]